Guide to the Robert Pinsky Papers
Department of Special Collections
- Series I. Correspondence
  - Subseries: General
    - R-S, misc:
      - Savory, Teo (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Schulman, Grace (The Poetry Center) (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Schmidt, Michael (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Shapiro, Alan (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Shapiro, Harvey (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Shore, Jane (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Sleigh, Tom (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Sommer, Jason (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Spacks, Patricia (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Sperch, Stephen (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Spires, Elizabeth (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - St. John, David (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Strand, Mark (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - T-Z, misc:
      - Tillinghast, Richard (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Toliver, Harold (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - University of Chicago (Edwin J. Kolb) (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Updike, John (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Voight, Ellen Bryant (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Wagoner, David (Poetry Northwest) (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - White, Gina (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Winters, Janet (Lewis) (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Wiseman, Marjorie (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Yamamoto, Traise (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Zeiger, Lila (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Unidentified
      - Unidentified (Bob, Michael, Mona, Paul, Pete, Rose, Steve) (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - B-G, misc.
      - Brumer, Andy (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Christopher, Nicholas (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Davie, Donald (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Dennis, Carl (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - D'Evelyn, Thomas (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Dougherty, Kate (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Ferry, David (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Fitzgerald, Penny Laurens (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Fussell, Paul (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Glück, Louise (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - Goldensohn, Barry (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - Gunn, Thom (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - H-L, misc.
      - Hall, Donald (Box 18, Folder 15)
      - Hass, Robert (Box 18, Folder 16)
      - Hall, Joan (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - Halliday, Mark (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - Halpern, Daniel (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - Hamilton, Ralph (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - Hartman, Charles (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - Hathaway, William (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - Heller, Mike (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - Hillman, Brenda (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - Hirsch, Edward (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - Hollander, John (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - Howard, Richard (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - The Hudson Review (Frederick Morgan) (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - Hyde, Lewis (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - Kenyon, Jane (Box 18, Folder 18)
      - Lee, Li-Young (Box 18, Folder 18)
      - Lewis (Winters), Janet (Box 18, Folder 18)
      - Levine, Phil (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - M, misc.
      - McHugh, Heather (Box 18, Folder 19)
      - McMichael, James (Box 18, Folder 20)
      - Martz, Louis (Box 18, Folder 21)
      - Matthews, William (Box 18, Folder 21)
      - Meredith, William (Box 18, Folder 21)
      - Mindwheel (photograph) (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - P, misc.
      - Princeton University Press (Mrs. Arthur "Jerry" Sherwood) (Box 18, Folder 22)
      - Peck, John (Box 18, Folder 23)
      - Pinsky, Robert (outgoing to his daughters) (Box 18, Folder 23)
      - Porbous, Katrina (Box 18, Folder 23)
      - Powell, Jim (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - R-W, misc.
      - Ryan, Michael (Box 18, Folder 24)
      - Sacks, Peter (Box 18, Folder 24)
      - Stern, Gerald ("Jerry") (Box 18, Folder 24)
      - Wakoski, Diane (Box 18, Folder 25)
      - Weiss, Ted and Renee (Box 18, Folder 25)
      - Williams, C.K. ("Charlie") (Box 18, Folder 25)
      - Wright, Charles (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Unidentified
      - Unidentified (incl. "Ellen and Steve," Laura, Peter) (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - A-G, misc:
      - AGNI (Ashold Melnyczuk) (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - The American Book Review (John Tytell) (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - The American Scholar (Joseph Epstein) (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - Antæus (Daniel Halpern) (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - Chicago Review (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - Cornfield Review (Marilyn Weston, Ohio State University) (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - Crews, Frederick (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - Columbia: A Magazine of Poetry (John Harney) (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - Dunn, Stephen (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - Eberhart, Dick (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - Fenza, David (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - Gettysberg Review (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - Goldstein, Stephanie (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - Graham House Review (Bruce Smith) (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - Grossman, Allen (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - Gunn, Thom (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - H-L, misc:
      - Hall, Donald (Box 20, Folder 16)
      - Halliday, Mark (Box 20, Folder 17)
      - Hass, Robert (Box 20, Folder 17)
      - Heaney, Seamus (Box 20, Folder 17)
      - Howard, Richard (Box 20, Folder 17)
      - Lea, Sydney (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - M-O, misc:
      - McHugh, Heather (Box 20, Folder 18)
      - Moss, Howard (Box 20, Folder 19)
      - Massachusetts Review (Paul Jenkins) (Box 20, Folder 20)
      - Maxy's Journal (E.M. Bennett) (Box 20, Folder 20)
      - Michigan Quarterly Review (Lawrence Goldstein) (Box 20, Folder 20)
      - Missouri Review (Shirod Santos) (Box 20, Folder 20)
      - Modern Language Quarterly (William Matchett) (Box 20, Folder 20)
      - Occident (Demetra Georgis) (Box 20, Folder 20)
      - Ostriker, Alicia (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - P-R, misc:
      - Peck, John (Box 20, Folder 21)
      - Palmer, Michael (Box 20, Folder 22)
      - Parnassus (Herbert Leibowitz) (Box 20, Folder 22)
      - Pequod (Mark Rutman) (Box 20, Folder 22)
      - Poetry (John Nims, Joseph Parini) (Box 20, Folder 22)
      - Ryan, Michael (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - S-U, misc:
      - Sandeen, Ernest (Box 20, Folder 24)
      - Sequoia (Gordon Harvey) (Box 20, Folder 25)
      - Simon, Kate (Box 20, Folder 25)
      - Tar River Poetry (Peter Makuck) (Box 20, Folder 25)
      - Tendril (George Murphy) (Box 20, Folder 25)
      - Three Penny Review (Wendy Lesser) (Box 20, Folder 25)
      - Urthkin (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - W-Y, misc:
      - Williams, Charles K. (Box 20, Folder 26)
      - West Branch (Box 20, Folder 27)
      - Western Humanites Review (Larry Levis) (Box 20, Folder 27)
      - Witness (Peter Stine) (Box 20, Folder 27)
      - Yale Review (J.D. "Sandy" McClatchy) (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - A, misc:
      - Agenda (Peter Dale) (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Allen, Dick (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - American Poetry Review (Stephen Berg, Eleanor Wilner) (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Atlantic Monthly (Peter Davison) (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - B, misc:
      - Biggs, Mary (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Bogen, Don (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Boyers, Bob (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Brown, Helen (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Brumer, Andy (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Barnstone, Tony (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Bly, Robert (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Bromwich, David (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - C, misc:
      - Cain, Bill (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Canfield, Cass (Harper Collins Publishers) (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Carnochan, Brigitte (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Cheuse, Alan (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Chicago Review (Keith Tuma) (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Chickering, Howell (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Concerning Poetry (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Columbia University (Towers, Lehman, Knubel) (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Contemporary Literature (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Contemporary Poetry/Poesis (Tom Jackson) (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Cutler, Bruce (Wichitaw State University) (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Carcanet New Press Limited/Carcanet Press Limited (Michael Schmidt) (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Collier, Michael (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Corey, Stephen (and Lola Haskins) (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Corn, Alfred (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - Corn, Alfred, (Notes from a Child of Paradise) (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - Crase, Douglas (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - Crews, Frederick (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - Cunningham, J.V. (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - D-G, misc:
      - Doherty, Paul (Box 22, Folder 15)
      - Dougherty, Kate (Box 22, Folder 15)
      - Dunham, Rob (Box 22, Folder 15)
      - Davie, Donald (Box 22, Folder 16)
      - Des Pres, Terence (Box 22, Folder 17)
      - Dickey, James (Box 22, Folder 18)
      - Djerassi, Carl (Box 22, Folder 19)
      - Duncan, Robert (Box 22, Folder 20)
      - Ferry, David (Box 22, Folder 21)
      - Ferry, David (Box 22, Folder 22)
      - Fine Arts Work Center in Provinceton (Susan Slocum) (Box 22, Folder 23)
      - Fitchen, Allen (University of Chicago Press) (Box 22, Folder 23)
      - Gibran II, Kahlil (Box 22, Folder 24)
      - Graff, Jerry (Box 22, Folder 25)
      - Gunn, Thom (Box 22, Folder 26)
      - Gunn, Thom (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - H-J, misc:
      - Halley, Anne (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Harvard Magazine (Christopher Reed) (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Hathaway, Kit (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Helfgott Hyett, Barbara (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Holt, Patricia (SF Chronicle) (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Hoagland, Tony (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Hongo, Garrett (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Humanities Institute Conference (incl. Jerome McGann) (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Hall, Donald (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Hall, Donald (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Halliday, Mark (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Halliday, Mark (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Halliday, Mark (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Hamilton, Ralph (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Harcourt Brace Jovanich, Inc. (incl. David Rosenberg) (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Hillman, Brenda (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Hirsch, Edward (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Howe, Irving (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Howe, Marie (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - Johns Hopkins University (Larzer Ziff) (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - Joseph the Provider Booksellers (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - K-L, misc:
      - Alfred A. Knopf, Inc. (Alice Quinn) (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Kalstone, David (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Kenner, Hugh (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Kenyon Review (Ronald A. Sharp) (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Kowit, Steve ("A Whitman Portrait") (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Leibowitz, Herb (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Levine, Phil (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Kolb, Barbara (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - Laughlin, J. (Box 23, Folder 16)
      - Lehman, David (Box 23, Folder 17)
      - Lewis (Winters), Janet (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - M-O, misc:
      - McHugh, Heather (Box 23, Folder 19)
      - Modern Occasions (Cheryl Walker) (Box 23, Folder 19)
      - The New Republic (Ann Hulbert and others) (Box 23, Folder 20)
      - Occident (Box 23, Folder 21)
      - Olds, Sharon (Box 23, Folder 21)
      - Osborn, Marijane (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - P, misc:
      - The Paris Review (Jonathan Galassi) (Box 23, Folder 22)
      - Pastan, Linda (Box 23, Folder 22)
      - Plumly, Stanley (Box 23, Folder 22)
      - Pomegranate Editions (Karyle Klopp) (Box 23, Folder 22)
      - Powell, Grosvenor (Box 23, Folder 22)
      - Poesis (Tom Jackson) (Box 23, Folder 22)
      - Poets and Writers (Frazier Russell) (Box 23, Folder 22)
      - The Providence Athenaeum (Michael Price) (Box 23, Folder 22)
      - Pushcart Press (Box 23, Folder 22)
      - Palmer, Michael (Box 23, Folder 23)
      - Parini, Jay (Box 23, Folder 24)
      - Parish, Michael (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Parkinson, Thomas (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Parnassus (Herbert Leibowitz) (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - John Peck (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Peseroff, Joyce (Greenhouse) (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Pickering, Jr., Samuel (Children's Literature) (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Ploughshares (DeWitt Henry, Joyce Peseroff) (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Poetry Magazine (Joseph Parisi, Helen Klaviter, John Nims, Dick Allen) (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Pollak, Felix (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Powell, James (Occident) (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - Pritchard, Bill (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - Prunty, Wyatt (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Q-S, misc:
      - Quarry West (Kevin Mitchell) (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - Rector, Liam (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - Salzinger, Leslie (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - San Diego Poet's Press (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - San Jose Poetry Center (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - Scott, Joanna (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - The Seattle Review (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - Shapiro, Alan (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - Shelley Memorial Award (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - Shore, Jane (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - Slusky, Joseph (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - Sonora Review (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - Sorkin, Adam (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - South Carolina Review (Bob Hill) (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - Southern Review (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - Spacks, Barry (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - Stern, Dick (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - St. John, David (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - St. John, Richard (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - Stoenescu, Stefan (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - Stone Country (Judth Neeld) (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - Studies in Romanticism (Sam Schulman) (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - Sacks, Peter (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - Salchert, Brian (Box 24, Folder 16)
      - Salter, Mary Jo (Box 24)
      - Schultz, Robert (Epoch Magazine) (Box 24, Folder 17)
      - Schwartz, Lloyd (The Boston Phoenix) (Box 24, Folder 18)
      - Scott, Peter Dale (Box 24, Folder 19)
      - Sheidley, William (Box 24, Folder 20)
      - Silberman, Steve (Box 24, Folder 21)
      - Simic, Charlie (Box 24, Folder 22)
      - Slavitt, David R. (Box 24, Folder 23)
      - Sleigh, Tom (Box 24, Folder 24)
      - Sleigh, Tom (Box 24, Folder 25)
      - Smith, Bruce (Box 24, Folder 26)
      - Smith, David (Box 24, Folder 27)
      - Snyder, Gary (Box 24, Folder 28)
      - Solotaroff, Ted (Harper & Row) (Box 24, Folder 29)
      - Spiegelman, Willard (Box 24, Folder 29)
      - Stern, Gerald (Box 24, Folder 30)
      - Stiller, Nikki (Box 24, Folder 31)
      - Summers, Marilynne (1 of 3) (Box 24, Folder 32)
      - Summers, Marilynne (2 of 3) (Box 24, Folder 33)
      - Summers, Marilynne (3 of 3) (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - T-U, misc:
      - Thorburn, David (Box 24, Folder 35)
      - Talbott, Jack (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Tikkun (Michael Lerner) (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Tendril (George Murphy) (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Turkey Press (Henry Reese) (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Telescope (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - University of California Press (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - V, misc:
      - Vanity Fair (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Vendler, Helen (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Voight, Ellen (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - VERSE Magazine (Henry Hart) (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - von Hallberg, Robert (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - W, misc:
      - Wellesley College miscellaneous (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - WIGWAG (Alexander Kaplen) (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Williams, Charles K. (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Williams, Charles K. (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Williams, Charles K. (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Williams, Charles K. (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Williams, Charles K. (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - Williams, Charles K. (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - Williams, Charles K. (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - Williams, Charles K. (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - Williams, Charles K., "A Dream of Mind," galley (Box 25, Folder 14)
      - Williamson, Alan (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - Williamson, Alan (Box 25, Folder 16)
      - Williamson, Alan (Box 25, Folder 17)
      - Williamson, Alan (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Unidentified:
      - Unidentified and Miscellaneous, incl: Pinksy phonelist, anonymous comments on Pinsky poetry, Levi (Walker?), Ramlay, "Susan [Pinsky's sister] & Marc" (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - C-F, misc.
      - Corn, Alfred (correspondence, poetry, prose) (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Daniel, David (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Denver Quarterly (Bill Ramke) (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Feldman, Irving (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Fergusson, Francis (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Ferry, David (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Fitzgerald, Robert (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - G-H, misc.
      - The Gettysburg Review (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Goddard College (Ellen Bryant Voight) (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Godine, David R. (publisher) (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Graff, Jerry (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Granta (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Grossman, Allen (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Guerard, Albert (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Guerard, Maclin (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Hall, Donald (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Harvard Magazine (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - I-N, misc.
      - Indiana Review (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Kenyon, Jane (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - New England Review (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - The New Republic (Ann Hulbert) (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - The New Yorker (Alice Quinn) (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - P-Q, misc.
      - The Paris Review, (Jonathan Galass) (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - Parini, Jay (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - PEN Syndicated Fiction Project (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Perloff, Marjorie (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Ploughshares (Don Lee) (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - PN Review (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Poetry Ireland Review (Chris Agee) (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Powell, Anthony (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Quarterly West (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - S-W, misc.
      - Salmagundi (Bob Boyers) (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - Salt Hill Journal (Michael Paul Thomas) (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - Southwest Review (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - TriQuarterly (incl. Reginald Gibbons, Alan Shapiro) (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - Three Penny Review (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - Wakoski, Diane (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - Wallace Stevens Journal (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - Wigwag: including Pinsky Galleys (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - Wilner, Eleanor (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - C.K. (Charlie) Williams (correspondence, poetry: 1990-1994) (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - C.K. (Charlie) Williams (correspondence, poetry: 1994-1995) (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - C.K. (Charlie) Williams (poetry, prose) (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Unidentified
      - Unidentified (incl: "Garry") (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - A-D, misc.
      - Academy of American Poets (1984-1993) (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - Agnes Scott College (Christopher Ames) (1988) (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Allston Brighton Art Exposition (1989) (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Amherst College (1990) (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Atlantic Monthly (James Atley) (n.d.) (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Baycon (San Francisco Bay Area Regional Science Fiction and Fantasy Convention) (1987) (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Berkeley, UC (1986-1989, n.d.) (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Berkeley Poetry Review, Pinsky and Thom Gunn reading (n.d.) (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Boston University, Playwright's Theatre (1991) (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Briarwood Writers' Alliance, Inc. (Bill Thompson) (1987) (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - California Institute of the Arts (1986) (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Central Connecticut State University (clipping) (c. 1992) (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Cincinnati, University of (1991) (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Collier, Michael 34 3 Connecticut, University of (1992) (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Converse College (1993) (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Dante's Inferno correspondence: Boston University Art Gallery, Pinksy/Michael Mazur exhibit (1995) (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Dante's Inferno correspondence: Pinsky/Mazur, various engagments (1992-1995) (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - DIA Center for the Arts, Pinsky/Louise Gluck exhibit (1993) (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - F-I, misc.
      - Fine Arts Work Center (1992) (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Fresno, California State University 34 7 George Mason University (1992) (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Georgetown University, Folger Poetry Series (1994) (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Georgia Poetry Circuit, Georgia State University (1988-1989) (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Groton School (1989) (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Harvard University, The Poets' Theatre, Helen Vendler (1988-1989) (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Hawaii, University of (1986) (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Image of Violence Conference (Society for the Interdisciplinary Study of Social Imagery) (Will Wright, Steven Kaplan) (1995) (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Iowa, University of (1985-1986) (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Irvine, UC (1985) (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - L-O, misc.
      - Larry Blake's (Berkeley) (1986) (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Lehto, Leevi (1992) (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Library of Congress (1992) (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Martha's Vineyard Writers' Workshop on Poetry: Charles Simic, Steven Orlen, Heather McHugh, Linda Pastan (1983) (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Mazur/Pinsky collaboration, "Image and Text: A dialogue with Robert Pinsky and Michael Mazur" an "Occasional Paper" of the Doreen B. Townsend Center for the Humanities, UC Berkeley, proof copy (1994) (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - Mazur/Pinsky collaboration, "Image and Text": correspondence: UC Berkeley, Christina M. Gillis, Doreen B. Townsend Center Newsletter 34 11 Massachusetts at Amherst, University of (1988) (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - Massachusetts Bay Community College (1993) (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Massachusetts at Boston, University of (1988) (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, the writing program (1988) (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Miami Book Fair International (1993) (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Michigan, University of, Hopwood Program (1989) (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Minnesota, University of, "The Responsibility of the Poet" talk by Pinsky (1985) (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Modern Poetry Association, Chicago: Marianne Moore Symposium (1987) (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Mount Holyoke College (Mary Jo Salter) (1991) (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Nielson, Michael (1986) (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - Noe Valley Poetry (1986) (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - North Carolina at Greensboro, University of (1992) (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - Old Dominion University (1993) (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - Olds, Sharon (1988) (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - P-S, misc.
      - The Poetry Center (92nd St. Y, New York) (Karl Kirchwey) (1989-1991) (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - Poetry Ireland Review, "Special North American Issue" (1995) (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - The Portland Poetry Festival (Greg Simon) (1982-1983) (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - Proceedings (n.d.) (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - Readings by Writers (Boston) (1989) (Box 34, Folder 13)
      - Recursos de Santa Fe (1985) (Box 34, Folder 13)
      - Rhode Island College (1990-1991) (Box 34, Folder 13)
      - Riverside, UC (1987-1988) (Box 34, Folder 13)
      - Rochester, University of (1991-1992) (Box 34, Folder 13)
      - Salina Arts and Humanities Commission (Salina, KS) (1986-1993, n.d.) (Box 34, Folder 14)
      - San Jose Poetry Center (1985-1987) (Box 34, Folder 15)
      - Share Our Strength, Bill Shore (1994) (Box 34, Folder 15)
      - Simic, Charles (1990) (Box 34, Folder 15)
      - Skeath, Meredith, Maharashi International University, University of Iowa (1985) (Box 34, Folder 15)
      - Southern Colorado, University of (1995) (Box 34, Folder 15)
      - Speak Out (1991) (Box 34, Folder 15)
      - St. John, Richard, Pittsburgh International Poetry Forum, University of Pittsburgh Contemporary Writers Series (1983-1984) (Box 34, Folder 15)
      - Stevens Institute of Technology (1985-1987) (Box 34, Folder 15)
      - Sweet Briar College, VA (1986) (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - T-Y, misc.
      - TIKKUN (1989) (Box 34, Folder 16)
      - Travel Service, Berkeley (1985) (Box 34, Folder 16)
      - U.S. News (1990) (Box 34, Folder 16)
      - Utah, University of (1991) (Box 34, Folder 16)
      - Vermont College of Norwich University (1991) (Box 34, Folder 16)
      - Virginia Commonwealth University (1988) (Box 34, Folder 16)
      - Walker Art Center, Minneapolis (1982) (Box 34, Folder 17)
      - Washington, University of (1989) (Box 34, Folder 17)
      - Washington and Lee University (1985-1986) (Box 34, Folder 17)
      - Wisconsin at Milwaukee, University of (1992) (Box 34, Folder 17)